

PROFILE

I am a UI/UX Designer with 3+ years of experience, working to help companies and individuals convey their ideas through design. With a business-first approach, I look to identify weaknesses in products to build impactful solutions at a low cost.

EXPERIENCE

UI/UX Designer - Mighty

January 2017 - Present

Responsible for the implementation of user flows, experiential design, as well as development of the user interface for new features. Collected various pieces of user-data to ensure proper modifications of the platform and tailor new features based on feedback. Assisted software engineers and front-end developers to ensure pixel-perfect delivery of completed features.

Freelance Designer

2011 - Present

Provided design consultation to identify weaknesses in the user experience and user interface of multiple web platforms. Assisted in the brand and landing page development of an online learning platform for foreign Chinese students attending American universities. Revamped the web interface of Front Office Sports, an inside sports blog, from a non-responsive to responsive site, resulting in an increase of page visits by over 400%.

UI Designer - Thuzio

May 2014 - December 2016

Influenced and Integrated Julius, an influencer marketing SaaS platform, by developing a new logo, brand colors, enhancing the UX of the web platform, as well as coding web assets. Chartered the redevelopment of Thuzio Executive Club, accommodating 200+ members, serving as product manager and lead designer constructing all UI elements. Implemented the launch of Thuzio 360, by developing a new company logo, brand colors, the UX of the web platform, as well as, executed design assets such as landing pages to code.

EDUCATION

BA, Graphic, Interactive & Advertising Design

2010 - 2014

Seton Hall University

(Minor: Business Administration)

DETAILS

jlacus@me.com 860.305.2323 josephlac.us

153 Valley Street Unit 130, South Orange, NJ 07079

TOOLS

Sketch InVision

Photoshop Slack

Illustrator

InDesign

PASSIONS

UI Design

UX Design

Product Development

KNOWLEDGE IN

Agile HTML/CSS

Prototyping SCSS

SaaS Wireframing







